Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
  - Branch Office Reports Bk. 3
    - Food drinks (Horlick's malted milk) consumer investigation and miscellaneous, 1939 June
    - Test on Smarties (Chocolate candy beans) (London), 1939 June
    - Distribution of interviews (Canadian population), 1939 Dec.
    - Survey on gum shortage--N.Y. metro area (Chicago Office), 1942 Dec.
  - J&J Colman Ltd (See also reels #38 and #196)
    - Distribution of dry mustard in 4 leading cities, 1933 Aug.
    - Dry or powdered mustard preliminary memo, 1933 Sept.
    - Per capita sales of Colman's mustard by units, 1934 Feb.
    - Investigation of dry mustard sales of 6 N.Y. wholesalers, 1934 Apr.
    - Office investigation bathing habits (Already in reel #196), 1935 Mar.
    - Investigation among clubs and restaurants, 1936 Mar.
    - Test preference for 4 premiums for Colman's mustard, 1938 Mar.
    - Investigation preference for 3 premiums among suburban housewives, 1938 Apr.
    - Test on Colman's mustard baths, 1938 Apr.
    - Colman's mustard test cities, 1939 Feb.
    - Presence of mustard in the home (6 cities tested), 1939 May
    - Plan for Colman's mustard tests in Women's Day and N.Y. Times magazine section, 1940 Jan.
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Bk.24. Fleischmann's Yeast (See also reels #49, #54-56, #59, #196,and #233)
      - Use of yeast for dogs in Westchester County, 1938 Aug.
      - Study of Vi-Syneral and Vitamin Plus, 1938 Sept.
      - Voice test for producer of Lux Radio Theater, 1938 Sept.
      - Doctor's opinions on Yeast Bulletin (Foil yeast), 1938 Oct.
      - Voice test for producer of Lux Radio Theater, 1938 Oct.
      - Fleischman's foil yeast--Advertisement recommendations--1939, 1938 Dec.
      - Irradiated dry yeast for dogs, 1938 Dec.
      - Analysis of Fleischmann foil sales and advertisement 10 months 1938 vs. 1937 and trends divisions with radio advertisement., 1938 Dec.
      - Advertisement and sales--Dry yeast for dogs, 1938 Dec.
      - Use of vitamins in bread, 1939 Jan.
      - Per capita bread consumption, 1939 Jan.
      - Foil yeast (Ex. household) trend of per diem sales in divisions with radio, 1939 Mar.
      - Trend of foil sales (Total per diem), 1939 May
      - Fleischmann foil yeast copy tests--Spring 1939, 1939 May
      - Sales trend in divisions with radio (1st 4 months), 1939 May
      - Fleischmann's Forvitan--Consumer test of Forvitan Trenton, 1939 jun.
  - R.T. French Co. (See also reels #39 and #196)
    - 15 sales units, 1933 Sept.
    - Effect on French's mustard sales--without a carton, 1933 Oct.
    - French's tapioca box, 1933 Nov.
    - Direct selling and delivery for French and Colman product, 1933 Nov.
    - French's mustard sales in leading cities, 1933 Sept.
    - Per capita sales of cream salad by units, 1934 Feb.
    - Sales trends by territories-1933 vs. 1932, 1934 Mar.
    - Tapioca pudding investigation, 1934 Mar.
    - Advantages of N.Y. area as a market for French's mustard, 1934 Apr.
    - List of grocery chains not carrying Worcestershire Sauce, 1934 jun.
    - Investigation of dealer's attention toward special sale of 6 oz. jar French's mustard and Hot Dan spoons, 1934 Sept.
    - Sales in 1st 4 months--1935 vs. 1934, 1935 May
    - Information on companies selling products through grocery store, 1936 slept
    - Report on Buffay sauce (S.M.A Corp.), 1936 Sept.
  - Lever Brothers. (See also reels #46, #47, #233, #250, #251)
    - Lux Flakes
      - Figures on soap flakes (from Crislede), 1932 May
      - Consumer response to Lux in general laundry, 1933 Jan.
      - Dealer attitude toward Lux Flakes, 1933 Feb.
      - Follow up on consumer response, 1933 jun.
      - Investigation on washing men's socks and underwear, 1933 July
      - Office investigation runs in stockings, 1933 Aug.
      - Consumer investigation on care of men's socks, 1933 Sept.
      - Lever Brothers vs. JWT--Report on washing men's socks, 1933 Sept.
      - Estimates of advertising expense of Chipso and Super Suds, 1933 Nov.
      - Rumor--Procter & Gamble--new medicated soap, 1934 July
      - Memo--Unprofitability of Lux for men's shirts, 1934 July
      - Voice test for producer of Lux Radio Theater, 1936 Apr.
      - Survey in N.Y. City on habits of washing dresses, 1936 Aug.
      - Radio ratings--Lux vs. other leading programs, 1937 Jan.
      - Consumer opinions on dish washing ads, 1937 Mar.
      - Office investigation--Method of washing dresses, 1937 Apr.
      - Office investigation--Laundering of hosiery, 1937 May
  - New Business (See also reels #49, #51, #52, #54)
    - Data on the market in the U.S. for hair preparation, 1937 Aug.
    - Annual sales of appliances for domestic use, 1937 Oct.
    - Proposed Woolworth outline for national survey, 1937 Oct.
    - Consumer analysis survey and cigarette consumption, 1937 Nov.
    - Office investigation on tints and dyes, 1937 Nov.
    - Cellophane cigarette packaging, 1937 Nov.
    - Consumer interviews on 20 selected articles--Woolworth story, 1937 Nov.
    - Windshield wiper investigation, 1937 Dec.
    - Analysis of half and half sales (Tobacco), 1937 Dec.
  - New Business (See also reels #49, #51, #52, #54)
    - New Business Bk. 16
      - Reader interest--By types of editorial content, 1937 Nov.
      - Trico products--Survey of auto replacement part, 1937 Dec.
      - Analysis of cough remedy sales--Drug stores, 1938 Jan.
      - Test of Robinson's lime and barley water, 1938 Jan.
      - Consumer survey on uses of mouth wash, 1938 Jan.
      - Information on crackers for children, 1938 Jan.
      - Dealer and consumer investigation on paper milk container, 1938 Jan.
      - Cigarette smoking habits survey in N.Y and Chicago, 1938 Apr.
      - Cigarette sales--Advertisement expenditures and costs, 1938 May
      - Drug products survey, 1938 May
      - Survey on attitude of public toward life insurance, 1938 July
    - New Business Bk. 17
      - Office investigation on tomato juice, 1938 July
      - Market analysis factors--Ward Baking Co. bread territory, 1938 July
      - Newspaper lineage placed by leading agencies for 100 leading advertisers, 1938 Aug.
      - Misc. data on General Electric, 1938 Aug.
      - Data on table sauces, 1938 Aug.
      - Store front interviews variety store A shoppers--Trenton, 1938 Sept.
      - House-to-house survey of housewives buying habits, 1939 Sept.
      - Sales of cough medicines and cough drops, 1940 Sept.
      - Investigation on effect of Schick razor retail price reduction in 7 cities, 1941 Sept.
      - A study of the market for 5 cent candy bars, 1942 Sept.
      - Test of dandruff remedy among JWT office member, 1943 Sept.
      - Trend in sales and advertisement costs of 3 leading brands of cigarettes, 1943 Oct.
    - New Business Bk. 18
      - Sales of mouth wash in chain drug stores, 1938 Nov.
      - Department store advertisement on back page of the N.Y. Times, 1938 Dec.
      - Hand soaps and household cleaners in paste form, 1938 Dec.
      - Information on sales of cold remedies and antacid products and trends of brand preferences for tooth pastes and tooth powders, 1938 Dec.
      - Plan for personal finance Company--Invest in St. Louis, 1938 Dec.
      - Plan and consumer survey--Gillette razor blade, 1938 Dec.
      - Public's attitude toward labor--Companies and Corporation, 1938 Dec.
      - Investigation among radio outlets on Stromberg--Carlson, 1939 Jan.
      - Facts about General Electric and Hot Point--Survey made for Easy Washing Machine Corporation, 1939 Jan (Reel 257)
      - Recent estimates of the total dog food market, 1939 Jan.
      - Report on public opinion study (big business and labor), 1939 Feb.
      - Report on cleaning and polishing preparation (Sherwin-Williams), 1939 Feb.
      - Monthly liquor tax collections in U.S. during 1938 and liquor sales in Pa. during 1938 (Martini l Rossi), 1939 Mar.
    - New Business Bk. 19
      - Percentage of persons that sleep well, 1939 Mar.
      - National Dairy Produce Corp.--Several plans for analysis of problems, 1939 Mar.
      - Office survey on radio sets (G.E), 1939 Apr.
      - Survey conducted among 2000 radio dealers by radio retailing, 1938 Apr.
      - Office test on Sylox powder (antiseptic), 1939 Sept.
    - New Business Bk. 20
      - Miscellaneous information about Baltimore (for Sylox powder), 1939 Sept.
      - Dealer interviews on Arret (Bath tub spray), 1939 Nov.
      - Office survey on smoking habits--Information about Old Gold, 1939 Nov.
      - Office investigation on silverware, 1939 Nov.
      - Cigarette display in Hartford. Conn., 1939 Dec.
      - Trend in record and phonograph industry, 1940 Jan.
      - Office investigation on cough drops, 1940 Jan.
      - Survey among JWT's members on long size cigarette, 1940 Mar.
      - Data on the Edison scholarship, 1940 Mar.
      - Kitchen tests--Alice Bailey's ready to serve foods and Aunt Bebe macaroon paste, 1940 Apr.
      - Interviews with buyers on bath oils and bath salts, 1940 Apr.
      - Home use of prepared bandages--Consumer survey, 1940 June
      - The trend of liquid dentifrices, 1940 July
      - Memo--on Frizz ice cream mix, 1940 July
      - Knox unflavored gelatin--Report by 9 leading grocery chains and wholesalers--N.Y., 1940 July
      - Survey on use of skin preparation for babies, 1940 Sept.
      - Nationwide vitamin survey, 1940 Sept.
    - New Business Bk. 21
      - Survey on use of skin preparations for babies, 1940 Oct.
      - Office cigarette survey, 1940 Oct.
      - Test of Frizz ice cream, 1940 Oct.
      - Pazo--Ointment--Charts, 1940 Oct.
      - Denver Chemical Mfging Co., 1940 Oct.
      - Pazo ointment--Sales comparisons, 1940 Nov.
      - Canadian vacation travel, 1940 Nov.
      - Report on Pazo ointment--Remedies for piles, 1940 Dec.
      - Memo--Alice Bailey's butterscotch pudding, 1940 Dec.
      - Survey on plated silverware--N.Y. and Chicago, 1940 Dec.
      - Suggested research studies (N.Y. subways) to make car cards more sellable, 1941 Feb.
      - Brooklyn chamber of commerce, 1941 Mar.
      - Memo--Electrical appliance survey in Hartford, 1941 Mar.
      - Office survey on car ownership, 1941 Mar.
      - Analysis of home consumption of various flavors of desserts, 1941 Mar.
      - Rough guide to potential sales of puddings by cities (Alice Bailey), 1941 Apr.
      - Alice Bailey survey in Norfolk, Va., 1941 Apr.
      - Alice Bailey consumer survey in Wilmington, Del., 1941 May
      - Alice Bailey projected volume of sales--Actual Wilmington, 1941 May
      - Metropolitan district market factors (American home), 1941 May
      - Questionnaire for grocery survey (American home), 1941 May
    - New Business Bk. 22: citrus fruits (Part 2: Part I out. charged to Mr. Edward, 11/25/46)
      - Presentation to the Florida Citrus Commission, 1938 June
  - Northam Warren
    - Cutex (See also reels-#38, #39, #59, #60, and #197)
      - Test of Cutex polishes (328B-297T and 328A-297A), 1937 Sept.
      - Nation-wide mail survey among beauty shops, 1937 Oct.
      - Inventory of Cutex liquid polish in 4 cities, 1937 Dec.
      - Nail polish test on application and wearing qualities, 1938 Feb.
      - Syndicate store beauty parlors, 1938 May
      - Test of Cutex foundation polish with Cutex regular crème polish, 1938 June
      - Test of nail beautifier, 1938 Sept.
      - Cutex liquid polish test--A vs. B, 1938 Oct.
      - Summary of manicure and nail products surveys (1923--1930s), 1939 Jan.
      - Office investigation on cuticle remover, 1939 Jan.
      - Total U.S. nail preparation sales and charts, 1939 Feb.
      - Nail polish check in beauty salons, 1939 June
      - Cutex 10 cents size dealer survey conducted in 6 cities, 1939 Aug.
      - Peggy Sage test on Nail Flex, 1939 Aug.
      - Drying test of Peggy Sage, Cutex and Revlon nail polish, 1939 Aug.
      - Test of nail polish remover--Regular vs. x-2966, 1940 Feb.
  - Scott Paper Co. (See also reels #53 and #54)
    - Scott mail investigation among doctors, 1932 Oct.
    - Consumer jury test of 4 types of Scottissue advertisement, 1933 Sept.
    - Analysis of replies to letters sent to office building in Atlanta, Ga., 1935 June
    - Consumer investigation on towels and tissue in Bridgeport, Conn. and Trenton, N.J., 1936 Nov.
    - Preliminary surveys on Boston, Cleveland, Detroit and Chicago, 1936 Dec.
    - Scott towel and tissue investigation in 6 cities, 1937 Jan.
    - Waldorf consumer investigation on copy appeal, 1937 Jan.
    - Scott mail survey among Binghamton office tenants, 1938 Dec.
  - Sharp & Dohme (See reel #54 also)
    - Confidential facts on the Sharp & Dohme business, 1932 Apr.
    - Facts on price reduction policy, 1932 Mar.
    - Facts on the drug market, 1932 Mar.
    - Analysis of consumer ad of Listerine, Pepsodent antiseptic and S.T. 37, 1932 Feb.
    - Analysis of prescription (Preliminary report), 1932 Feb.
    - Points for discussion in meeting, 1932 Feb.
    - Replacing unprofitable business with profitable business, 1932 June
    - 3 year plan for national introduction of Haxyl-Resorcinol toothpaste, 1932 June
  - International Department
    - International advertising (149 pp. report on JWT as an international agency, with brief reports on individual offices. Starts with overall summary of JWT in 1935, charts, client lists), 1935
    - Great Britain (13 pp. with advertisements and charts), 1899-
    - Antwerp (5 pp.), 1927-
    - The Hague (37 pp., mostly demographic information), 1927-
    - Bombay (8 pp.), 1929-
    - Bucharest (4 pp.), 1930-
    - Buenos Aires (5 pp.), 1929-
    - Copenhagen (6 pp.), 1927-
    - Cape Town (6 pp.), 1928-
    - Paris (5 pp.), 1927-
    - Sao Paulo ( 5pp.), 1929-
    - Sidney (7 pp.), 1929-
    - Toronto (2 pp.), 1930-
    - Montreal (6 pp.), 1929-
    - Belgium--A key to the reading habits of people with money (Report on the results of contest organized by General Motors Continental among car and truck owners in Belgium--Joint property of General Motors and Agence Thompson; 171 pp. with examples of ads), 1937 June
    - Berlin and Paris--Trends in display advertising (prepared by Display Department, JWT London, with illustrations), 1933
    - South America goodwill tour (Jan 20 through Nov. 29, via Pan American Stratoliner) by John Strohm (Assistant Editor of the Prairie Farmer)--mainly reprints of magazine articles, including country-by-country reports (Through page #57 only papers #58 through #73 cont. on reel #283), 1941
  - Carter Products
    - Calsamate--Plan for 3 inv., 1942 Mar. (Reel 337)
      - Nationwide survey of headache, 1942 Mar.
      - Survey of physicians in 3 cities--N.Y. Chicago, 1942 May
      - Consumer test of headache tablets, 1942 May
      - Superior--Dist. 2 display check in Syracuse, Binghamton, 1942 Dec.
      - Plan for intensive consumer survey--Endicott and Binghamton, 1943 Mar.
      - Consumer survey in Syracuse and Binghamton, 1943 May
      - Distribution check in San Francisco and Los Angeles, 1943 Sept.
      - Office test of superior as headache and cold remedy, 1944 Feb.
      - Superior free offer survey--N.Y. Daily News, 1944 Mar.
      - Dealer survey on distribution, 1944 Aug.
  - Northam Warren
    - Cutex
      - Test of Peggy Sage Jewel polish and Cutex Opaline polish, 1940 Mar. (Reel 338)
      - Test of Cutex regular oily polish remover vs. Cutex oily polish, 1940 May
      - Survey on manicure sets, 1940 May
      - Copy test--Cutex current advertising, 1940 May
      - Test of Cutex salon type polish, 1940 June
      - Peggy sage gloves vs. mittens, 1940 Aug.
      - Northam Warren sales territories, 1940 Sept.
      - Investigation of nail polish in Walgreen stores--Chicago, 1940 Sept.
      - Data on adv. expenditures and sales organization of certain cosmetic Company, 1940 Nov.
      - Office test of Peggy Sage c-18A vs. regular, 1940 Nov.
      - Investigation on nail polish in Walgreen stores--Chicago, 1940 Nov.
      - Test of Peggy Sage c-18A vs. regular, 1940 Dec.
      - Summary of Cutex tests--1937 through 1940, 1940 Dec.
      - Charts--Starch ratings of Cutex advertising, 1941 Jan.
    - Cutex Bk. 9
      - Consumer investigation on all manicure preparations, 1941 Jan.
      - Additional charts on Cutex investigation (sec. 1), 1941 Feb.
      - Test of Cutex cuticle rubber applications, 1941 Mar.
      - Peggy Sage nail polish test (mad apple and dusty rose), 1941 May
      - Consumer investigation in New Haven on manicure preparations, 1941 Aug.
      - Memo to: Wm. Resor re: use of 1 or 2 coats of polish on nail, 1941 Oct.
      - Memo to: Wm. Resor re: retail price changes of drugs, cosmetics etc., 1941 Oct.
      - Test of Cutex polish--X-4220, 1941 Nov.
      - Memo to Mr. Resor re: retail price changes of drugs, cosmetics etc., 1941 Nov.
      - Memo to Mr. Resor re: odor test of Cutex polish G-192A and g-192-B, 1941 Dec.
      - Information on nail polish--Publication surveys, 1942 Mar.
      - Total U.S. sales of Cutex preparations--Charts ( 1937-1942), 1943 Jan.
      - (1 sec Odorono) survey of stores on displays, 1943 Jan.
      - Nail polish survey in variety stories in 14 cities, 1943 Nov.
      - Comparative display space variety by store, 1943 Dec.
      - Memo to: Wm. Resor re: brittle nails, 1944 Jan.
      - Memo to: Wm. Resor re: Cutex liquid polish test, 1945 Feb.
      - Dealer survey on manicure sets, 1945 Aug.
      - Office survey on nail polish drier, 1945 Oct.
      - Office survey on nail polish drier and cuticle remover, 1945 Oct.
      - Survey in variety stores on display space for manicure program, 1945 Dec.
      - Memo to: Wm. Resor re: magazine survey information on brands of nail polish, 1945 Apr.
      - 2nd survey in variety stores, 1946 Apr.
      - Test of polishes 123 a vs. 123 b-123 c vs. 123 d, 1946 May
      - Office test of nail polish formulas--R vs. S; O vs. P, 1946 July
      - Office test of nail polish formulas--E vs. F; G vs. H, 1946 Sept.
    - Cutex Bk. 11
      - Fact finders nail polish test--A vs. B; C vs. D; E vs. F; G vs. H, 1946 Oct.
  - Easy Washing Machine
    - Easy Washing Machine Bk. 2
      - Nation-wide consumer survey, 1938 July
      - Intensive dealer survey in 40 centers and their immediate trading areas (92 places covered), 1938 July
    - Easy Washing Machine Bk. 3
      - Investigator's reports of impressions in 40 centers and their trading areas, 1938 Aug.
    - Easy Washing Machine Bk. 4
      - Analysis of 1587 Easy dealers based on reports secure from the outlets by Easy salesmen, 1938 Oct.
      - Analysis of the effect of Easy's present adv. policies with specific conclusions and recommendations, 1938 Nov.
      - Estimate of washing machine potential market in Rings N.Y. and Perry Co., Ky. based on a market factor of home owners, 1939 June
  - R.T. French Bk. 4
    - Consumer survey on household bluing in N.Y.C. (Reckitts) Atlantis Sales, 1936 Oct.
    - Test of two mustards (French vs. Gulden), 1937 June
    - Personal interviews with 305 housewives in N.Y. City, 1938 Sept.
    - Comparison of two mail surveys identically conducted 1937 and 1938, 1938 Sept.
    - Manufacturer's value of condiments and sauces, 1938 Nov.
    - Brand preferences in homes (Scripps-Howard inventory), 1939 Feb.
    - Total sales--Atlantis Sales Corp.--1938 vs. 1937, 1939 Feb.
    - Report on thick meat sauces (and later revised corps--March 1940), 1939 May
    - Interviews with wholesalers and chain grocers (N.Y.C) on 5 cent size prepared mustard, 1939 Sept.
  - Miscellaneous Office Reports
    - General Information Bk. 2
      - Consumption of castor oil in pounds, 1939 Feb.
      - Weighted index of drug variety and dept. stores sales in U.S., 1939 Feb.
      - Distribution of families by income level, 1935-1936, 1939 Apr.
      - How grocery clients handle special discounts, ads, allowances, 1939 June
      - Outline of Consumer Panel plan on 7 products, 1939 July
      - Headache remedy test campaigns, 1939 Nov.
      - Summary of publication surveys, 1939 Dec.
      - Consumer--Dealer--Mail surveys in N.Y. Chicago and S.F, 1939, 1939 Dec.
      - Premium study--Mr. Hosch, 1937 May
      - Information on shredded coconut, 1940 march
      - Frequency of visiting a grocery store, 1941 Feb.
      - Possible display of national defense material, 1941 Apr.
      - Paul Stewart and Associates and the Trademark Foundation, 1941 May
      - Some effects of the defense program on local retail marketing, 1941 May
      - U.S. city water supply, 1941 Sept.
      - Possible retail outlets for juke boxes, 1941 Sept.
      - Items included in each classification of national advertising, 1941 Oct.
      - Hair dye, 1941 Oct.
      - Estimated analysis of female population by age groups 1940, 1941 Dec.
      - Places suggested as test towns for developing civil defense methods, 1941 Dec.
      - 1943 estimated population vs. 1940 census--N.Y, NE. N. Jersey metropolitan area, 1943 July
      - Post--War grocery distribution, 1943 July
    - General Information Bk. 2a
      - Memo to: Mr. Hosch: re: trends in retail food costs vs. trend in retail price of white bread--Average of 56 cities, 1939-1943, 1942 July
      - Trends in retail food costs vs. trend in retail price of white bread, 1943 July
      - Republican National Finance Committee (Not here--but in a H J file under R), 1943 Aug.
      - Memo to: Miss Waldo re: baking powder production, 1943 Dec.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lever Brothers vol. 1
      - Vimm's test of five proposed Vimms ads, 1944 Feb.
      - Vimm's corps test of proposed Vimms ads, 1944 march
      - Vimm's 2nd test of two proposed headlines, 1944 march
      - Copy test of two proposed Vimms headlines featuring minerals, 1944 Apr.
      - Nationwide check on dealer substitution, 1944 Apr.
      - Vimms dealer survey, 1944 Apr.
      - Office surveys (2) on taste of Vimms, 1944 May
      - Summary of the 1st unaided recall Vimms survey in Chicago, 1944 May
      - Nationwide Consumer Panel survey, 1944 May
    - Lever Brothers vol. 2
      - Outline of car card surveys in Chicago, 1944 June
      - M.S. population of 1940 by age groups--U.S. census, 1944 June
      - New York Office survey on 3 Vimms packages, 1944 Aug.
      - Memo to: McCullough re: Vimms copy, 1944 Aug.
      - Survey on Frank Sinatra signature Song, 1944 Aug.
      - Memo to: Howard re: composition of audience of Sinatra Vimms program, 1944 Aug.
      - Survey of families sending for free samples--N.Y. news, 1944 Aug.
      - Memo to: Stevens re: Vimm's radio audience surveys, 1944 Dec.
      - Memo to: McCullough re: check of preference for Vimm's container, 1945 Jan.
      - New York Office copy test--Vimms, 1945 May
      - Summary on use of Vimms--New York Office, 1945 July
      - Memo: Mr. Swanson re: Canadian survey on Rinso Sneeze, 1940 Aug.
      - Memo: Mr. Swanson re: suggested method of protecting copy for Rinso, 1940 Aug.
      - Proposed 1940-1941 research program for Lever Brothers Ltd., 1940 Sept.
      - Plan for radio effectiveness continuing survey, 1940 Oct.
      - Revised suggestion for continuous survey, 1940 Oct.
      - Comments on effectiveness of Odex couponing, 1940 Oct.
      - Cumulative vs. weekly graphs--All Canada, 1940 Feb.
      - Cumulative vs. weekly graphs--Quebec, 1940 Feb.
      - Readership of car cards, 1941 Apr.
      - Memos: Mr. Dobbs re: Lifebuoy What a Life ads, 1942 Sept.
      - Memos: Mr. Dobbs re: consumer survey of Lypsyl, 1943 June
      - Preliminary shampoo study--Canadian consumer survey, 1944 Aug.
  - Navy Air Force